export default data = [
  {
      question: "I enjoy drinking a cup of black coffee ______ Friday nights",
      options: ["at","by","in","on"],
      correct_option: "on"
  },
  {
      question: "It's raining ______. I think you should stay here until the rain stops",
      options: ["politely","heavily","clearly","easily"],
      correct_option: "heavily"
  },
  {
      question: "This restaurant is ______ for its chicken soup. Many people come to eat it",
      options: ["crazy","delicious","famous","sharp"],
      correct_option: "famous"
  },
  {
      question: "Lisa's room was very dirty. It took her three hours ______ it",
      options: ["clean","cleaned","has cleaned","to clean"],
      correct_option: "to clean"
  },
  {
      question: "It's cold outside; ______ sure to put on your coat before you leave the house",
      options: ["be","it is","being","it will be"],
      correct_option: "be"
  },
  {
      question: "Tommy uses chopsticks well, but his younger brothers ______, so they usually eat with spoons",
      options: ["don't","doesn't","aren't","isn't"],
      correct_option: "don't"
  },
  {
      question: "Jane is going fishing tomorrow. She wants to know ______ the weather will be fine",
      options: ["how","what","whether","why"],
      correct_option: "whether"
  },
  {
      question: "David forgot to bring money with him, so I ______ him NT$60 to pay for his lunch",
      options: ["borrowed","lent","ordered","spent"],
      correct_option: "lent"
  },
  {
      question: "Why don't we have a ______ for our singing group? I think it looks great when everybody in a group wears the same thing",
      options: ["party","program","test","uniform"],
      correct_option: "uniform"
  },
  {
      question: "The tall man ______ at the bookstore is my high school teacher",
      options: ["you saw","who saw","you saw him","that you saw him"],
      correct_option: "you saw"
  },
  {
      question: "Stella: Is this Simon's book?  I found it under the chair. Joyce: No, it's ______ Thank you. I've been looking for it",
      options: ["I","me","my","mine"],
      correct_option: "mine"
  },
  {
      question: "Shirley: How's your new English teacher?  She looks friendly. Lauren: She is nice! ______, she's the nicest person I've ever seen",
      options: ["Even so","In fact","However","Also"],
      correct_option: "In fact"
  },
  {
      question: "Doris: Why ______ so many things to do when I'm busy enough? Frank: That's because you don't know how to use your time well",
      options: ["does it have","have","are they","are there"],
      correct_option: "are there"
  },
]
